Raktim Ranjan Deka

Guwahati, Assam, INDIA

□ (+91) 7035913286 | ■ raktimnewdeka@gmail.com | □ Raktim167 | □ raktim-ranjan-deka-075bb7183

Career Objective

I've been working as a front-end web developer for around 2 years, and now seeking a new challenge. I think my experience and skills in JavaScript, ReactJs, HTML and CSS make me perfect for this role. I've worked on large development projects that have sharpened my technical skills, improved my communication and made me understand what it takes to meet tight deadlines with excellence.

Experience

NATIVEBYTE Noida, India

SDE-1 APRIL 2022 - Present

- Worked with many projects such as real estate, university-student course app, bank website, Information Portal etc with skills of React, Strapi, HTML, Tailwind, Redux etc
- Worked on different UI Technologies

NETMEDS.COM Chennai, India

SDE-1 Sept 2021 - March 2022

- Worked with Trinity Team as a Developer
- · Worked on different UI Technologies

Skills_

Languages JavaScript, ReactJs, HTML, CSS, SQL, Strapi, NextJs, Tailwind CSS

Database MySQL

Interest OS, DBMS, OOPs, Web Development

Tools POSTMAN, MYSQL WORKBENCH, Microsoft SQL, VISUAL STUDIO CODE

Education

BARAK VALLEY ENGINEERING COLLEGE, KARIMGANJ

BACHELOR OF ENGINEERING (COMPUTER SCIENCE ENGINEERING)

· Percentage: 80.14

CALVUVACUL HUNDOD COLLEGE CHIMALIATI

SENIOR SECONDARY EXAMINATION - CLASS XII (AHSEC)

• Courses: Maths, Physics, Chemistry, English, Alternative English.

Karimganj, India

Aug 2017 - Sept 2021

SAI VIKASH JUNIOR COLLEGE, GUWAHATI

Guwahati, India

2017 batch

Projects ___

1. CAR DETAILS Guwahati, India

REACT PROJECT July 2023 - August 2023

the applications will be listing out many cars and it will allow the searches for the car brand and car model, it will be listing out different cars, also it is mobile responsive

RESPONSIBILITIES:-

1. development and testing.

TECHNOLOGIES and TOOLS USED:- JavaScript, React, Tailwind, RapidApi, NextJs

2. PROPERTY LISTING WEBSITE

Guwahati, INDIA

DBMS Project June 2023 - Sept 2023

the applications will be listing out different properties in different cities or global location and also it will allow the searches for a particular city and can be used various filters with which user can get desired property, and inside desired property details page they can see all sorts of images, amenities, google maps, layout etc

RESPONSIBILITIES:-

1. front-end.

TECHNOLOGIES and TOOLS USED:- HTML, CSS, React, Tailwind.

Achievements ____

HackerRank HackerRank, India

5 STAR RATING

July 2020

• https://www.hackerrank.com/raktimyumi167

CODECHEFCodechef, India

3 STAR RATING

August 2020

• https://www.codechef.com/users/raktim1607